JARED S. DALEY B.Sc., COMPUTER SCIENCE

25163 52 Avenue Langley, BC V4W 1G1 604-996-3427 • www.jareddaley.com • work@jareddaley.com

 HTML5 / CSS3
 SQL
 Prolog

 ● ● ● ● ● ●
 C/C++
 Sys. Admin.

 ● ● ● ● ● ●
 GIT

 Python
 Haskell
 Adobe Suite

 ● ● ● ● ● ● ● ●
 ● ● ● ● ●

I am familiar with Windows, Mac OS, and Linux, as well as the Android, iOS and WebOS mobile operating systems.

My main focus in the field of Computing Science is web development, with a particular interest in front-end design and functionality.

Proficient in computer diagnostics and repair; have performed as an occupation and as a hobby.

Worked for four years as a graphic designer using the Adobe suite of design programs, including Illustrator and Photoshop. The majority of my work dealt with corporate identity, such as the design of business cards, letterhead, and signage.

Interested in the media arts; have done various projects involving music and video production, as well as photography and photo editing.

SELECTED PROIECTS

Vertical Search Engine (Teachr)

2013

Front end designed using Twitter Bootstrap • Back end made using Python and PHP, as well as the Codelgniter framework • Javascript and jQuery Elements • Spelling correction and search suggestion

N-Body Collision Detection Simulator

2013

5-Person Group Project • Helped conceive and create a TCP Framework for Socket Message Passing on Multi-Threaded System • Dealt with Locking/Unlocking POSIX Threading • C and Python Based

go.SFU Replacement Website (UniReg)

2012

3-Person Group Project • Created and implemented front end from scratch • Some Twitter Bootstrap elements used • Heavy UI/UX Emphasis • Took Clojure/Javascript back end and made UI work with it

Scheduling Software

2011

Programmed in Java using the Netbeans IDE • Designed and programmed the entire GUI in Swing • Managed user interface integration with back end functionality.

JaredDaley.com

Ongoing

As with all websites, my personal site's development is never finished • Programmed using PHP and Codeigniter Framework for back end • Twitter Bootstrap and custom elements for front end

EMPLOYMENT

HireTheWorld, Junior Developer

2012

Helped maintain website day-to-day • Fixed reported bugs, with emphasis on cross-browser compatibility (specifically IE) • Implemented new features and ideas from myself and others • Mainly PHP, HTML, CSS and Javascript development • Agile-based Development Paradigm • Helped improve affiliate program and used SEO to refactor site to perform at optimal levels in page ranking

Bourquin Printers and Signs, Graphic Designer

2008-2012

Designed various logos, signs, plaques, advertisements, promotional materials, and office stationery for companies in the surrounding area • Responsible for various customer service and office tasks in a high stress and time-sensitive environment • Provided computer and printer repair services for the company • Produced finished high-quality printed materials.

TechService.ca, Computer Service Technician

2007-2008

Completed computer repair tasks, including hardware and software maintenance • Performed web design tasks using Dreamweaver and Photoshop CS3.

EDUCATION

Simon Fraser University, Bachelor of Science (Computer Science)	2007-2013
Graduated with a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and a final GPA of 3.21.	

Rick Hansen Secondary School

2003-2007

Graduated with a 4.0 GPA, and honours, including top media arts student.

Abbotsford Virtual School

2006-2007

Graduated with Web Design 12, A+ 12, as well as Cisco CCNA training.

AWARDS

Dean's Honour Roll, Faculty of Applied Sciences, SFU	2012
NSERC Undergraduate Student Research Award	2012
Summit Scholarship, Simon Fraser University	2007
British Columbia Provincial Scholarship	2007

INTERESTS

SPORTS: Played football as an offensive lineman in both community and high school leagues for 8 years.

MEDIA ARTS: I play 5 musical instruments including: piano, clarinet, saxophone, drums, and guitar. I write and produce music recordings as a hobby. I also enjoy video production and photography.

TECHNOLOGY: As a result of building, fixing and maintaining computers for most of my life, I have developed an avid interest in technology. I am a talented digital illustrator and web designer. I am also an avid collector of electronics, both vintage and new, and have a passion for mobile technology.